Cinderella
Cinderella's Sister
Episode 6
This is Kyung Wha Chung.
Don't you remember anything?
You're so simple...
Can you just forget it all if you choose to?
Do you really not have anything to say to me?
Let go!
Let go of me! Let go!
Eun Jo.
Eun Jo...
Whoever you were, how you smiled, or what your name was.
None of that matters now.
You're nothing more than a bug or mote of dust to me.
Calling my name and smiling at me.
I dare you to do it. Then really, I'll just kill you.
Son, did you have a bad dream?
It was just a dream so don't cry, my son.
This horrible punk.
You little punk.
This adorable, horrible punk.
This little, little, adorable punk.
My son.
Everyone went on a picnic
without me.
Without me.
What is it?
You can leave now.
There are lots of others who can do research on yeast.
I didn't think you were staying around with a plan to leave.
You were clear and brave. Not only was your brain fast but so is your feet.
If you want to fly,
I plan on giving you wings.
I've never thought
that you had to ever say anything bad to me, not once.
I know.
You know?
Yes.
You don't know that. You don't.
If you knew, you wouldn't have thought of a plan like that.
I've never thought of you as different from Hyo Seon.
(as his daughter)
Well, I guess there may have been times.
But that's in my subconsciousness,
that I neither am aware of nor want to know.
Even if you say I've hidden away something like that in my subconscioues,
I wouldn't think that of you.
I thought you thought of me the same way.
Give me your plans.
I... have the right to know at least that much.
If you've been here only for the purpose of paying back a debt,
you must have had other thoughts in your mind.
Things you've wanted to do, how much you've prepared,
or how you're going to live out in the world.
At the very least, since I've changed your surname from your mom's to mine,
and I've been the guardian of a child named Goo Eun Jo,
I deserve to know your plans for the future.
I'll give it to you.
My plans.
Okay. You can leave now.
Are you letting Eun Jo leave?
Let's talk about this later.
Are you leaving?
Are you chasing us out?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Are you chasing me and Eun Jo out right now?
Honey,
I didn't think something like this would happen again.
If I did something wrong, forgive me!
Darling, I must not have satisfied you with all my shortcomings.
But still... I really gave it my all.
I don't even know what's good, but tried to be good no matter what.
Honey!
Seriously...
Honey, Honey!
Honey! Listen. Why are you being like this?
Listen to me!
Mom!
Honey!
What?
I said let's get married.
I've decided on that, so you should decide on that, too.
Decide on what?
To marry me.
Okay, sure.
No matter how much you like Eun Jo, I won't allow it.
If even you go to Eun Jo, what will I have left?
Hyo Seon...
You're mine.
Since you've agreed to be mine, don't change your mind.
Doctor, is she going to be okay?
You don't have to worry, she'll be fine.
- Come this way, I'll see you off.
- Alright.
Where's Joon Soo?
Are you okay?
Joon Soo is at Ichon, don't worry.
Where's your father?
He's escorting Hyo Seon's grandfather home.
Don't say anything. You're weak right now.
Outside... is anyone there?
No one is there.
I said don't speak.
You bitch. You crazy bitch!
Why would you leave?
If you just stay like this, the factory, the house, and the company
could become entirely yours and Joon Soo's.
What nonsense are you speaking, talking about leaving?
I was relieved
because I thought you understood what you had to do.
But what? Leave?
So...
you put on a show?
It's weird to take back something you've already said,
so just say you can't leave seeing how uneasy it makes my mother.
Use me as your excuse, okay?
I can't do this. Get me some water.
I'm not like before.
If I act like I'm fainting, I'll faint for real!
I should've just...
What? What are you saying?
I should've just died.
What?
I had so many opportunities to die.
There were so many opportunities
for me to not be involved with you.
What are you murmuring?
Omo...am I hearing things?
You just try saying something like that again.
Then, I'll really show you things you shouldn't see.
Go get me ice water!
Mom!
I'm okay.
Did I not hear something?
What?
Did you say something to me?
Are you here on an errand?
It's not an errand...
Then is the chairman looking for me?
Tell him I'll be there in the afternoon.
Noona.
You haven't told anyone about this, have you?
No.
I'm scared that someone's going to see this.
Even if you're upset by it, it's better than nothing.
Are you already paying me my salary?
It's not your salary.
There's just something like that.
Don't be curious about it!
Mom!
Joon Soo, mom's right here.
Mom! My toy gun!
Okay, I'll give you your toy.
♫  I feel I can reach you if I extend my hand ♫
♫  I see you in front of me ♫
♫ "Don't go", I cannot say those words yet ♫
♫  I must be standing here just looking toward you ♫
♫  Turn around please, Turn yourself around again please ♫
♫  If you go away like this, can you really live without me?  ♫
♫  You cannot go because I won't live even a day  ♫
♫  I'm still standing here staring at you  ♫
Don't you love yeast?
I like yeast the most in the world. I like it a hundred, a thousand times more than my husband.
Yeast doesn't play poker or cheat.
Please save me, little guys.
By the way, do you want to go on a blind date?
He's a great man who, unlike mine, doesn't play poker as his hobby.
I mentioned him to you last time.
I told him you didn't want to, so I declined once already,
but he won't give up and keeps asking. Huh?
Dae Seong True Winemakers
Until he finds a better place and walks out himself,
I won't send Gi Hoon away.
Gi Hoon is a pitiful child.
The reason he worked so hard, all by himself, to study
and came all the way here is because I'm here.
He came looking for my shadow because he was lonely.
You're arrogant. Do you know that?
Did you bring me your plan?
No.
Did you change your mind because of Mom?
If you had actually written up a report like I told you to, and waved it in my face,
I really don't know how I would've felt.
Good on you for not writing one.
I know that you're not one to starve to death, wherever you are.
That's not what I meant when I said I wouldn't have to worry about you wherever you end up.
I want you to find somewhere your heart is warm,
where it can stay without flailing around.
Until then, I want to take care of you.
You speaking as if you would leave after you've paid back you 'debts' to me?
It makes it clear you don't understand my intentions.
It wasn't for many days,
but my heart ached in misery after you said that.
Don't do that again, okay?
This house...
is difficult for me.
Don't give me affection.
If you have, take it all back.
I'm a horrible person.
You can't even imagine how wicked I am.
If you knew the kind of thoughts I have while living,
you wouldn't want to see me for even a second.
For now, I've been stopped by Mom, but I will leave eventually,
whether it be because I pay back my debts with my research or
because I get married to the man I'm meeting on my blind date.
So...
don't take a liking to me.
I'm not someone who will live in gratitude forever
just because you give me some trust.
What did you say?
I'll help you in other ways.
The work I'm doing right now doesn't
permit me to analyze finances or accounting.
Nor do I have a wish to have to approach those things if I don't need to.
Why did you have your mind?
Have you grown more fond of Goo Dae Sung-
I've not the Hong Gi Hoon from 8 years ago.
When I left that place, I threw my old self away.
Maybe that would be the case if I had never left, but once I did, I forgot everything.
Then why are you hesitating?
What do you mean, you don't want to approach it if you don't need to?
It's kind of similar to princes in the Joseon Dynasty fighting over the throne. Isn't it?
The son working to overthrow his father
and his father wants to strike down his son.
He gives his support to a hidden prince-
And on top of that, the prince that is of that worth
pounces on the person who took him in and ruins him.
Shut up, you bastard!
To use a sword to cut him up,
but the opponent is too young.
I'm ashamed of using a sword, so I put it away.
Dae Sung isn't your opponent.
You can ignore them.
What would you know?
I'm just resting there for a moment.
As I rest, I'll think of ways I can help you.
A way to double, triple, your strength without taking over Dae Sung.
A way to save you and not have the company stolen by Gi Jeong.
You say Dae Sung isn't our opponent?
Do you think they are?
You half-witted punk.
What is this?
Look at it.
It's a report of the number of times Gi Jeong has tried to purchase Dae Sung Co.
He's failed. Goo Dae Seong didn't put it up for sale.
Gi Jeong... isn't giving up.
I can't just let Gi Jeong purchase it.
Shall I tell you one more thing?
Do you know...
how your mother died?
My father is the chief surgeon at Myeongjin Hospital.
My mother is a professor in the design department of Seonhwa University.
My older brother is a prosecutor at the Seoul Metropolitan Prosecutor's Office,
and my younger sister is graduating from medical school this year.
I heard you weren't interested in anything about it.
To be honest, I was really curious about you, so I asked a lot of questions.
Is that so?
I was so shocked when I heard about you.
Why?
I heard you were the daughter of a rice wine company that is threatening Hong Joo Co.
Since Hong Joo is such a large company,
and Dae Sung Co was only known within the Daegu region up until just a few years ago.
I was surprised at the speed at which it's been growing.
I heard that Hong Joo is quite on edge these days, especially given they though Daeseong's growth was insignificant before?
Is that what you were curious about me?
How tall are you? 160 cm? 161cm?
How tall do I have to be for you to marry me?
- What?
- I'm asking how tall I have to be for you to marry me.
170cm? 171cm?
Why are you being like that? Do you have a complex about your height?
I don't care about such things.
If I were going to marry based on height, I should've met a model.
I wouldn't have asked to meet you.
Shouldn't you already have matured past the age of having a complex about something like your height?
You look about 165cm with your heels on.
That's enough for me. Showing off your inferiority complex like that isn't good!
Excuse me!
You're going on blind dates?
I guess you don't like him.
Judging from how quickly you left.
Hello?
Are you crazy? Slow down!
Slow down.
Drive slowly. I won't follow you. I'll go in front of you, come slowly.
The road winds a lot. A lot of accidents happen. Something bad could happen!
I won't chase you.
I won't try to hold on, and I won't ask for you to hold on to me.
So you don't have to try with all your might to escape to anywhere possible.
Okay?
I already...
Do you have something to say to me?
I'm only saluting someone who has fed me.
Salute, ma'am.
Calling...
Just promise me one thing.
If you take over Daeseong Co,
give it to me right away.
If you promise that,
I'll start working.
Why is our precious baby sitting here doing dirty work like this?
Go inside!
No, Granny. I have to do this. I can do well.
What do you mean, do it well. You're spilling half of it.
I'm going to do it well.
If they say to wash rice, I'll wash it. If they say to ferment the yeast, I'll ferment it.
And ...
I'm going to get married, too.
Won't you do it properly? Do you know what kind of rice this is?
This is rice grown without the tiniest bit of herbicides or chemicals.
It's organic rice grown by catching bugs with human hands.
Don't you dare spill a single grain. Do it properly!
I am. I mean I will do it.
Granny, am I useless?
What?
I'm going to do everything well.
I can do well.
Once you're done with that, come see me. I'll wait in your room.
Salute.
Shall I dance more for you?
No. You can take it off now.
What are you doing?
You're pretty.
You calling me pretty... it won't work anymore.
You're a liar.
I know you're just trying to make me feel happy by saying I'm pretty,
to get me to do whatever you want me to do.
I won't be tricked twice.
I'm glad.
Do you think I'll do whatever you tell me to do?
Won't you?
If not, tell me now. I thought you liked this.
This isn't something I'll force someone who doesn't want to do it to do.
If you won't do it, I can use money.
Your father's money.
You ...
are so wicked.
Are you not going to do it?
You won't, right?
Okay then.
Hey!
It's delicious.
One more time.
Again?
We haven't even started.
Okay.
Auntie, can you give us some more meat?
And another bottle of soju!
Give us rice wine instead of the soju!
Daeseong rice wine.
Why are you ordering alcohol when you can't even drink?
You drink all of it.
Two bottles of Daeseong's rice wine!
No, three bottles!
I think we'd better put Daeseong's logo on aprons and menus,
and give them out for free to all the pubs.
Make a plan and write a report.
Okay. I understand.
Oppa, you don't need your hands, because I'll be your hands.
- What are you doing?
- Open up!
You can't drink alcohol.
Hyo Seon, don't drink.
Why not?
You drive.
She's horrible...
I'm going crazy...
- Newbie!
- Yes, sir!
I feel like I've seen you around before.
What's your name?
My name is Han Jeong Woo.
You sound like a soldier. Are you?
It hasn't been long since I've returned.
And... I'm not just an ordinary soldier.
I was in the marines.
I see...
♫ In the solictude which wakes me up  ♫
♫ when I wake up from an exhausted sleep ♫
Unni!
♫ because I still remember you smiling ♫
♫ I'm secretly smiling ♫
Where did she go? She's not here either.
♫ Love leaves again this way ♫
I'll try looking around the outside, so you look inside the house.
Okay.
♫ When the beautiful season arrives ♫
Daeseong Company
♫ In the sadness you left in the longing ♫
♫ I walk this street again ♫
♫ I am living day after day  ♫
♫ In your name when tears appear, ah ♫
♫ I can't bear it, so I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again. ♫
♫ Even if there are wounds left in my heart now ♫
♫ I am told to forget about you ♫
♫ but even if I bite my lips and bear it ♫
♫ You are the only one who is my person ♫
♫ I am living  ♫
♫ day after day ♫
♫ In your name  ♫
♫ when tears appear again, woo ♫
♫ I can't bear it, so I can't laugh ♫
♫ I'll call out your name again ♫
Noona... What's so hard?
The airdrops that help me breathe.
Nature's grain wine
100% domestic, organically fermented
Daeseong Company Rice Wine
♫ In a small place in my heart ♫
♫ When longing comes again ♫
♫ In the thought of you again, unknowingly again ♫
♫ the tears soon will flow ♫
♫ More than saying you loved me ♫
♫ while you silently look at me  ♫
♫ I said I liked you so much and loved you ♫
♫ Today you must tell me ♫
♫ My love, will you run to me? ♫
♫ I too unconsciously am waiting for you. ♫
♫ Today for me is the day for your sake ♫
♫ I am going to love you this way ♫
♫ Now I'm not lonely (I'm not lonely,) ♫
♫ I won't cry again.
♫
♫ You are always living in my heart, ♫
♫ Stay with me ♫
♫ My love, will you run to me? ♫
♫ I too unconsciously am waiting for you. ♫
♫ Today for me is the day for your sake ♫
♫ I am going to love you this way ♫
♫ My love, will you run to me? ♫
Are there any more?
Where?
Yes.
Yes. I got it.
Where in Jeju Island?
Yes, I understand.
Yes.
How... how did this happen?
Is this what a TV advertisement does?
We have to wait to know if it's just temporary or will be constant.
We can't take any more orders. Turn them down.
Yes, sir.
Turn them all down?
We have to. Even with the orders we have right now, all our machines are being fully operated.
How can we make more?
I understand. Thank you.
We can take more orders.
We're getting support from the Ministry of Agriculture, Food and Rural Affairs.
They sent an auditor remember?
We got it.
With that, we can expand our lines.
Hyo Seon, go get some cotton from the pharmacy!
Okay.
I knew this would happen, okay? I knew it.
How could a person like you be so careless.
I'm fine, I'll hold it.
Stay still.
Hyo Seon! Hurry!
Eun Jo!
Song Eun Jo...
No, Goo Eun Jo...
I can't copy her.
I can't become like her.
If I try to become her, I will split rght in half.
As soon as I realized I can't catch up with her,
I wanted to cry.
It's not because she makes me uneasy,
but my tears wouldn't stop.
I swear to the heaven and the earth,
that everything I said to her was 100% a lie.
Unni...
Unni.
Don't die.
Don't die, Unni.
Just die...
That was an accident.
Unni, I'll be better.
I'll be kinder to you.
Don't die, Unni.
You got a bloody nose because you were picking it, right?
Asking her this was my sincerity.
Unni,
Shut up.
Unni.
I said shut up.
Unni...
What are you making a fuss?
Am I dying? Did they say I'm dying?
Or did you wish I would die?
Let go.
What are you doing?
You're the most wicked of them all.
I've never seen someone as wicked as you my entire life.
You want to make me worthless, don't you?
That's why you showed up at our house, right?
Where are you going? Don't you dare move!
I can't stand to watch you move.
I can't bear listening to you speak!
Spending endless nights in the labs to kiss up to Dad,
and getting a bloody nose.
Even if you don't do that, I get compared to you every day
and become more and more useless.
Then you, next to someone as useless as me,
only seem more impressive and diligent.
Try moving one more time.
Try fainting one more time!
I wish someone like you would just die!
What are you saying?
This little punk...
Hyo Seon.
Hyo Seon, stop right there!
Talk to me. Hyo Seon!
What's wrong?
Oppa... Hurry...
Take me.
What?
Hurry up!
They say you're fine. Just take some supplements and rest for a few days.
You're quite blessed. When even you're sick, you get to be sick so extravagantly.
Why are you working so hard?
It'll all become yours even if you don't work so hard, you little bitch.
What? Why?
In the past, when we used to live with that man when we were in Geunsan the time you made the noose...
Did you do that because you really wanted to die?
Are you crazy? Why would I die? It'd be too unfair if I died.
That guy in Geunsan, he would keep chasing after women.
But you really hung yourself. You could've died.
Do you think life comes to you as you want it?
Even if something bad happens,
you have to take risks to gain what you want.
You've still got a long way to go.
If I say I want to leave one more time,
you said you would show me things I shouldn't see, right?
I did.
Does that mean you can make another noose again?
Of course.
Is that all because of me?
Is that for me?
Does it seem like a lie?
I wish it were a lie.
I used to dig around trash bins with you on my back.
Even if it was dirty, I thought it would be better than not feeding you anything.
When you got sick from me feeding you things I dug up,
when you had a fever all night and your eyes flipped upwards
so far that I could only see white,
I prayed to Jesus, Buddha, and the deities
and told them to dare kill my baby.
I told them I wouldn't stay still.
The heavens and all, I would chew it up and swallow it whole.
I gave up on living with dignity on that night.
Do you know who I am?
I fought against Jesus and Buddha and won. To save you.
A noose?
I can make 100 nooses, you bitch.
There's no reason to be touched.
What mother in this world wouldn't do that?
Do you even like Hyo Seon's father?
Is Hyo Seon's father just someone you can take a lot from?
Oh?
You at least like Hyo Seon's father, right?
Why are you asking me something like that?
Tell me that you at least like him a little bit.
If you tell me that he's not just someone you can take a lot from,
but someone you like, then I'll forgive you.
Why are you making such a fuss?
I do like him, why? I like him!
I like him because he has a lot of things I can take from him! Why?
♫ It must be you. I cannot be without you. ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫ I don't mind even if I am hurt. ♫
♫ Yes, if it's just you, it is enough ♫
♫ because you are the only one I love. ♫